Kubo-chan, take off your pants.
くぼちゃん、パンツを脱いで
Raise one leg and knee in the direction.
片足、方向に膝を上げて
Take off your pants.
パンツを取ってみ
Please make yourself comfortable.
気持ちよくしてください
Do whatever you like.
好きにしてください
raise your mouth
口を上げて
please.
ください
It's big as is.
その まま大きいね
Please sit on top.
上からまたまってください
painful?
苦しい?
Try talking a lot.
いっぱい喋ってみ
Violently.
激しく
Kubo-chan, it's all in your mouth.
くぼちゃん、全部口の中です
Yo.
よ
Absorb every drop of my spirit
精 神一滴残らず吸い取って
please.
ください
Please take it all out.
全部 出してください
More intensely.
もっと激しく
Did everything come out?
全部出た?
Did a lot come out?
いっぱい出た?
I'll take a look.
見てみます
Please give it to me.
手に出してください
A lot came out.
すげえいっぱい出たね
It was amazing.
すげえろかったよ
It's cute.
可愛いし
Thank you.
ありがとうね